Make-Up@nicks.co.za 01645536697

Candidate Name: Nicolette Posthumus

Gender & race: Female, white ID: 9302220060082

Age: 24

Driver's License Yes – code 08
Languages English, Afrikaans
Home Country South-Africa
Current Country Vietnam, Hanoi



EDUCATION

HOERSKOOL DINAMIKA MATRIC, **2011**FACE TO FACE **2012 – 2014**

- City & Guilds Diploma for Beauty Therapy
- Diploma in Health & Skincare Diploma in Make-Up Design & styling
- Diploma in Beauty Specialist Diploma in Nail Technology
- Certificate in Relax Scalp Massage
- Certificate in Eyelash Extensions
- Certificate in Advance Make-Up & Styling
- Certificate in Airbrushing
- Certificate in make-Up Artistry
- Competency Certificate in Body Therapy, Image Consulting, Henna Tattoos, Fast Fashion Hair Styling & Photographic Workshop
- Attendance Certificate in Skin mate Skincare Product Training & Salon Specifics Product Training
- -First Aid Responder Certificate
- -PADI Swim School
- •Swim instructor course
- -i-to-l TEFL Course
- •TEFL Certification- 120 Hours
- -Pro-Ed
- Early Childhood Development Level 4 & 5 Diploma
- Child Care Experience: 2 year

CAREER SUMMARY

Jan 2012 – Apr 2012 TAX DATA
Position: Junior Bookkeeper

- Pastel accounting
- Invoice capturing
- Payments & receipts entries Filing
- General admin duties

Reasons for Leaving: Company closed down

August 2014 – October 2015: JONATHAN ANDREWS ACADEMY

Position: Make-up artist/ Lecturer

- Manual Publishing Course material
- Teaching Marketing Course sales
- Online Make-Up shop
- admin
- Photo Shoots
- Make-Up Applications
- Client meetings
- Office Admin duties

Reasons for Leaving: I moved to Randburg & due to unprofessional behaviour from the boss.

November 2015 – February 2016: Reddford House Northcliff Position: School Receptionist, Personal Assistant &HR

Receptionist:

- Face of the school
- Answering all calls to the school
- Handling walk in, future and current parents in a friendly manner
- Assisting to the best of my abilities the students, parents and teachers
- Ensuring parents and students feel comfortable, and leave the premises happy and satisfied with the service received
- Ensuring no one walks into the student area without authorization

Personal Assistant:

- Making all appointments for the MD
- All bookings for the MD such as flights, hotels etc.
- Maintaining the MDs diary
- Ensuring the MD is up to date at all times with regards to any incidents, complaints, compliments and staff queries

HR:

- Offer of employment
- Ensuring all documentation is received for each new staff member
- Ensuring all the staff members get their salary and over time etc.

Reasons for Leaving: Temporary contract for 3 months, left because of a teaching opportunity.

March 2016-August 2016: Magic Being Nursery & Swimming School Position: Teacher and Swim instructor

- Morning class teacher in baby centre age group 3 months to 1 year old
- Head Teacher in age group 4-5 years' old
- Afternoon sub teacher in age group 2-3 years' old
- Swimming teacher
- Preparation of lesson plans and reports
- Communicating with parents

Reason for leaving: I moved to China.

Currently working at:

New Youth Training School
Position:

English Teacher

Duties: Teaching kindergarten, Primary and middle school students english

Currently: Morning Star International Kindergarten

Position: Kindergarten Teacher

What I enjoy:

- Playing Hockey
- Coaching hockey and sports
- Ice Skating
- Spending time with family
- Playing around with make-up

Summary:

I am a trustworthy person who enjoys working with children and people and believe you must love what you do. I enjoy working hard and to make a difference in children's life even if it is just with a smile. As much as I enjoy learning I love assisting others in developing a skill or understanding a process. I am always willing to learn more skills and to push my boundaries as you can never have too much experience.